[Music]
[音乐]
so why don't we get started just a
那为什么不开始呢
couple minutes early I don't think
我不认为要提前几分钟
anybody's gonna make it in anyway
任何人都会成功
just let me start by saying I love this
我先说我爱这个
conference and I love all of you for
会议，我爱你们所有人
being at this conference there are a lot
在这次会议上有很多
of people in this room so I'm really
这个房间里的人，所以我真的
really happy we're here today to listen
非常高兴我们今天在这里听
to multi service reactive streams using
使用多服务反应流
spring reactor and our sock at a really
Spring 反应堆和我们的袜子真的
really long name I really have to work
长名字我真的必须工作
on naming I'm really really bad at it
在命名上我真的很不好
for those of you who don't know me
对于那些不认识我的人
haven't seen any of my talk so far this
到目前为止，我还没有看过我的演讲
week my name is Ben Hale on the lead of
星期我的名字叫本·黑尔（Ben Hale）
Java on Cloud Foundry which seems like a
Java on Cloud Foundry看起来像一个
really odd thing since I'm up here
真奇怪，因为我在这里
talking to you about reactive
与您谈论被动
programming in Java and here my day job
用Java编程，这是我的日常工作
is to run a cloud platform actually so
实际上是在运行云平台
why am I here
为什么我在这里
right why do I have this interest
对，为什么我有这种兴趣
clearly from the keynote and all of this
从主题演讲中可以清楚地看到
stuff reactive and the key thing is my
反应性的东西，关键是我的
position running on Java on cloud
在Java on cloud上运行的位置
foundry puts me in a position where I
铸造厂使我处于我所处的位置
see a lot of customers and a lot of
看到很多客户和很多
customer needs and when it came time to
客户需求以及何时
start talking about r2 DBC I saw how
开始谈论r2 DBC，我看到了
people were trying to connect the
人们试图连接
databases and this is a very very
数据库，这是一个非常非常
similar thing we see all of our
类似的事情，我们看到了我们所有的
customers coming to reactive programming
客户参加反应式编程
eventually it's a slow trickle now but
最终这是一个缓慢的trick流，但是
more and more we see that this idea of
我们越来越多地看到这种想法
high efficiency applications is really
高效的应用真的
really key to all of our developers
对我们所有开发人员而言，真正的关键
right in the long term no one wants to
从长远来看，没有人愿意
pay pivotal as much as they're currently
支付他们当前的关键费用
paying pivotal no one wants to pay
支付关键没人愿意支付
Amazon or Google what they have to pay
亚马逊或谷歌他们要付什么
what we need to do is get away from a
我们需要做的是摆脱
lot of the the things that we've done so
我们所做的很多事情
far when we were just running in our
当我们只是在我们的跑步中
data center and and computers were just
数据中心和计算机只是
sunk costs and so it didn't really have
沉没成本，所以它实际上并没有
to matter very much so we want to go to
非常重要，所以我们想去
reactive programming in just a quick
快速进行反应式编程
review for anybody who hasn't seen me
为没有看过我的人进行评论
twice before fundamentally non-blocking
在基本不阻塞之前两次
paired with asynchronous behaviors but
与异步行为配对，但
absolutely not a requirement for
绝对不是
asynchronous behaviors right reactive
异步行为正确反应
generally has no opinion on a
通常对
synchronicity the highest efficiency
同步最高效率
stuff if you take a look inside a
东西，如果你看看里面
project reactor the fastest stuff you'll
Project Reactor是您最快的东西
see running is reactor internally doing
看到运行在反应堆内部
a thing called fusion where they take a
他们称之为融合的东西
lot of your operations and they like
很多操作，他们喜欢
pull them
拉他们
out and glue them right next to one
把它们粘在旁边
another running exactly in the same
另一个完全一样
thread one after another directly
直接一个接一个地
connected cuz that is actually the
连接的cuz实际上是
fastest way to run reactive code however
但是，运行反应式代码的最快方法
when you want to do asynchronous kinds
当你想做异步种类时
of behaviors reactive really really
行为反应真的
works well the programming model makes
编程模型使效果很好
asynchronous kinds of things you might
您可能会异步的事情
even say possible right key
甚至说出可能的右键
differentiator we're gonna say from
我们要说的与众不同
asynchronous programming is this idea of
异步编程就是这个想法
pole pushback pressure this idea that a
极推压力这个想法
publisher can't send me any data unless
出版商无法向我发送任何数据，除非
I have first asked that publisher to
我首先请那个发布者
send me data so we see this slide that
给我发送数据，以便我们看到这张幻灯片
we saw at at the keynote the other day
我们前几天在主题演讲上看到了
composite health gives us the ability or
综合健康使我们有能力或
so reactive programming gives us the
所以反应式编程使我们
ability to now say I want this thing and
现在可以说我想要这个东西的能力
this thing to run in parallel with one
这个东西要与一个平行运行
another right these two things don't
另一件事，这两件事不
depend on one another they can happen at
彼此依赖，他们可能会发生
the same time they could happen
他们可能同时发生
sequentially if you think that's a
如果您认为那是一个顺序
better way to do it reactor but what I
更好的方法来做反应堆，但我
want you to do is go get me a URI go get
想要你做的就是去给我一个URI去去
me another URI and then once those two
我另一个URI，然后一次这两个
things have happened in parallel
事情并行发生
sequentially build me a composite out of
依序建立我的综合
that and this really is the key that
那真的是关键
reactive frameworks are giving you this
反应性框架正在为您提供
is the way they enable this high
是他们实现这一目标的方式
efficiency because now your
效率，因为现在您
declaratively basically saying parallel
声明性地基本上说平行
and then sequential right you never have
然后连续的权利，你永远不会
to manage the threading or the
管理线程或
optimizations behind-the-scenes to do
幕后优化
that but there are still road blocks
那，但仍然有路障
using reactive everywhere as I said I am
我说我在各处都使用反应式
personally a reactive everywhere person
个人随处可见的人
that is not the official policy of
那不是官方的政策
pivotal it's not the official policy of
关键不是官方政策
the spring team react it use reactive
春季团队反应使用反应
when you think it's right there are a
当您认为正确时，有一个
bunch of places where it's totally
一堆完全没有的地方
obvious this is where you want to use
显然这是您要使用的地方
reactor and there are a bunch of places
反应堆，还有很多地方
where it's not and it may not actually
在哪里，实际上可能不是
pay off so when we say using reactive
还清，所以当我们说使用反应式
everywhere everywhere that it's
到处都是
appropriate data access the data access
适当的数据访问数据访问
side has really been on top of reactive
方面真的是最重要的
MongoDB Cassandra Couchbase read it's
MongoDB Cassandra Couchbase阅读它的
those kinds of things these no sequel
这些没有后遗症的东西
data source really jumped on it they
数据源真的跳上了他们
were created in a time where this
是在这个
asynchronous plot programming model
异步绘图编程模型
especially driven by nodejs was really
特别是由nodejs驱动的
common and so they brought it over we've
常见，所以他们把它带到了我们
obviously started our to DBC as well
显然也开始我们进入DBC
because we know that relational
因为我们知道关系
databases are where all of your data
数据库是您所有数据的存放地
really is not these guys here so
真的不是这些家伙在这里吗
we want to make sure that's available at
我们希望确保可以在
the same time and then finally we want
同时，最后我们想要
to talk about cross process back
再谈一下跨进程
pressure which is a really complicated
压力真的很复杂
way of saying how exactly do I get
说我到底如何得到的方式
reactive programming across the network
跨网络的反应式编程
right I know that I can say okay a
对，我知道我可以说一个
publisher inside of my JVM can't send me
JVM内的发布者无法发送给我
any more data than I've asked for it but
比我要求的更多的数据，但是
now I got to go do an HTTP call to
现在我要进行HTTP调用
another micro service which is about to
另一个微服务即将
send me ten million rows adjacent right
向我发送一千万行相邻的权利
now I'm hosed and so I'm happy to not
现在我被抽水了，所以我很高兴没有
announce a project so much as point to a
宣布一个项目，以至于指向
project called our socket historically
历史上称为我们的套接字的项目
our socket was designed by the team
我们的插座是由团队设计的
inside of Netflix called the edge server
Netflix内部称为边缘服务器
routing team I believe it's what they
路由团队，我相信这就是他们
were called these are the people who
被称为这些是
brought you Netflix OSS previously they
他们之前给您带来了Netflix OSS
sat down and said okay
坐下来说好
Netflix OSS is great lots of people out
Netflix OSS吸引了很多人
there using hysterics lots of people out
有歇斯底里的人很多
there using Eureka things like that but
在那里使用尤里卡之类的东西，但是
we think we can do better right before
我们认为我们可以做得更好
we were sort of hamstrung internally we
我们内部有点受阻
knew we had to use HTTP or we had to use
知道我们必须使用HTTP或必须使用
TCP but what if that actually wasn't a
TCP，但是如果实际上不是
requirement what if we were really
要求如果我们真的是
really ambitious and said all of the
真的很雄心勃勃，并说所有
things that we want to do with HTTP all
我们想用HTTP做的所有事情
of the things we want to do with all of
我们想要做的所有事情
this high availability stuff like the
像
circuit breaker pattern of service
断路器服务模式
registries load balancing and
注册表负载平衡和
complicated ways what if we were more
复杂的方式，如果我们更多
ambitious and we said there's a network
雄心勃勃，我们说有一个网络
protocol that does that move way down
向下移动的协议
the stack underneath all of these
所有这些下面的堆栈
application servers running and
运行的应用服务器
coordinating with one another and so
互相协调等等
they came up with this great thing right
他们想到了这个伟大的事情
our socket is a bi-directional
我们的插座是双向的
multiplexed message base binary protocol
复用消息库二进制协议
based on reactive streams back pressure
基于反应流的反压
there's a lot of words in that we're
有很多话，我们
gonna take a look at every single one of
来看看每个
those words the next couple slides and
这些话，接下来的几张幻灯片和
it provides out-of-box support for the
它为
most common interaction models
最常见的互动模型
especially once you take channel into
特别是一旦您进入频道
account you realize it's a bailout and
帐户，您意识到这是一次救助，
you can do any kind of interaction model
你可以做任何一种互动模型
with it so what is a message driven
有了它，什么是消息驱动的
binary protocol mean right so if you
二进制协议表示正确，所以如果您
think about how HTTP is supposed to work
考虑一下HTTP应该如何工作
you make a request and you get a
你提出一个请求，你得到一个
response back much of that request so
回复大部分请求，因此
you get a document back effectively you
您可以有效地取回文件
call that a document based protocol a
称基于文档的协议为
single request returns you a document of
单个请求将返回您的文档
some kind whether it's HTML or it's
无论是HTML还是HTML
Jason or something
杰森之类的
like that when we talk about a message
这样，当我们谈论一条消息时
driven binary protocol what we're
驱动二进制协议是什么
talking about is all of the requestor
谈论的是所有请求者
responder interaction is broken down
响应者互动已分解
into a set of frames something very
变成一组框架
small that encapsulate individual
小封装个人
messages with inside of them rather than
内含而不是内含的讯息
a single blob of text going out and a
一小段文字外出和
single blob of something else coming
一滴其他的东西来了
back we get these discrete frames saying
回来，我们得到这些离散的帧说
this is a request so I can send a bunch
这是一个请求，所以我可以发送一堆
of requests independently of one another
彼此独立的请求
to you because this is a message that
给你，因为这是一条信息
says I want you to go get me something
说我要你去给我​​一些东西
and when it's time for you to respond
当你该回应的时候
you don't just sort of give me a
你不只是给我一个
firehose of bits you package them in
你把它们打包的firehose
little messages that are going to come
即将出现的小消息
back to me the framing is binary which
回到我的框架是二进制的
is really counterintuitive especially
真的违反直觉
coming from you know 20 30 years now of
来自你知道20 30年的
HTTP right it's so common for us to fire
HTTP正确，对我们来说很常见
up Wireshark or something like that some
Wireshark或类似的东西
of the proxying mechanism and just look
的代理机制，只是看
at the headers that are going by right
在右边的标题处
everybody knows what an HTTP request
每个人都知道什么是HTTP请求
looks like in ASCII text but what we
看起来像是ASCII文本，但是我们
find out is if you choose binary instead
找出是如果您选择二进制
it is incredibly smaller has much better
它小得令人难以置信
compression we have massive efficiencies
压缩我们拥有巨大的效率
for machine to machine communication and
用于机器对机器的通讯和
by the time we're talking about our
在我们谈论我们的时候
socket and the scale that sort of our
插座和我们的秤
socket wants you to work at this is a
插座要你在这工作
huge huge improvement over something
巨大的进步
like HTTP the overhead of the protocol
像HTTP一样，协议的开销
itself shrinks so much compared to the
与
data that's being transferred in it
在其中传输的数据
downsides manifest rarely primarily when
缺点主要在以下情况很少出现
you're trying for out why the hell
您正在尝试找出为什么
doesn't this work especially for people
这项工作对人特别不利
who work on our socket Java or our
在我们的套接字Java或我们的Java上工作的人
socket go or our socket Kotlin or
socket go或我们的socket Kotlin或
something like that but the the stacks
像那样的东西，但堆栈
the libraries that actually implement
实际实现的库
this protocol trying to debug this can
这个协议试图调试这个可以
sometimes be a giant pain but there's
有时会有巨大的痛苦，但是有
enough tooling in the world around you
您周围的世界中有足够的工具
can write Wireshark protocol
可以写Wireshark协议
sorry Wireshark plugins for example to
对不起，Wireshark插件例如
know how to decode the binary data as it
知道如何解码二进制数据
goes by and we can take a look at that
过去了，我们可以看看
the one key thing we've been talking
我们一直在谈论的关键一件事
about you know sort of message
关于你知道的信息
derivatives are the binary nature of
导数是
this protocol is that the payloads
这个协议是有效载荷
themselves are the exception to this
本身是例外
idea payloads are just bags of bytes
想法有效载荷只是字节包
right we don't the the protocol doesn't
对，我们不，协议不
actually tell you what a payload needs
实际告诉您有效载荷需要什么
to be doesn't need to be ASCII text it
不需要是ASCII文本
doesn't need to be Jason it doesn't need
不需要是杰森，不需要
to be
成为
buf to name another protocol GRP see
buf命名另一个协议GRP，请参见
that does advertise as very similar
广告确实非常相似
kinds of things to this so it could be
这样的事情，所以它可能是
Jason it could be XML if you're still
杰森，如果您仍然愿意的话，可能是XML
XML kind of people because internally
XML类的人，因为内部
the protocol says it's just a bunch of
该协议说这只是一堆
ones and zeros we're gonna give it to
一和零，我们要给它
the client or we're gonna give it to the
客户，否则我们将把它交给
responder or the requester at the end
最后的响应者或请求者
and they're gonna decode it the way that
他们将以这种方式对其进行解码
they want to the protocol itself is also
他们想要协议本身也是
multiplexed and this when I first got
多路复用，当我第一次得到
started with our socket was the most
从我们的插座开始是最
amazing epiphany I had about networking
关于网络的惊人顿悟
right so what does this mean
对，这是什么意思
connections that that only used a single
仅使用单个连接的连接
request are massively inefficient we saw
我们看到的请求效率很低
this in HTTP 1.0 and so HTTP 1.1 came
这在HTTP 1.0中，所以HTTP 1.1出现了
out and I said okay you've got a
我说好，你有一个
connection why don't you just send a
连接为什么不发送一个
bunch of requests and the order that you
一堆请求和您的订单
send them is the order you expect to get
发送给您您期望得到的订单
responses back from them oh trying to
回复他们，哦，试图
manage that yourself was always giant
确保自己永远都是巨人
pain most web frameworks would take care
大多数Web框架都会照顾自己的痛苦
of this for you but there were still
这个给你，但仍然有
issues right what happens if I send five
问题正确，如果我发送五个，会发生什么
requests over the single connection to
通过单个连接请求
you but the first one is really slow
你，但是第一个真的很慢
when the later four could have been
当后来的四个
really fast and this is why if you take
真的很快，这就是为什么如果你服用
a look at how a web browser works it
看看网络浏览器是如何工作的
doesn't open a connection for everyone
不能为所有人打开连接
really inefficient for every like
每个人的效率都很低
everything it needs to go get off of
它需要去的一切
your server doesn't open one for each of
您的服务器不会为每个服务器打开一个
those because lots of connections are
那些是因为有很多联系
inefficient but it also doesn't open
效率低下，但也无法打开
only one because now all of a sudden
只有一个，因为现在突然
slow requests can interfere with fast
缓慢的请求可能会干扰快速的请求
requests and more or less you're stuck
请求或多或少地被卡住
in a situation where your webs your web
在您的网站的情况下
page is likely to render only as fast as
页面的渲染速度可能仅与
the slowest possible thing no
最慢的事情
incremental loading so this is really
增量加载，所以这真的
really bad even an HTTP 1.1 multiplexing
甚至HTTP 1.1多路传输也非常糟糕
solves this issue it opens a single
解决了这个问题，它打开了一个
connection right a single physical
单个物理连接
socket or I guess depends on what you
套接字或我猜取决于您
think physical means physical socket
认为物理意味着物理套接字
between two servers and then it says
在两个服务器之间，然后说
okay within this pipe I'm gonna send one
好的，我要在这个管道中发送一个
message it says I'm stream one and then
消息说我流一个，然后
it's gonna send another message says I'm
它会再发送一条消息说我
stream three and those can return in any
流三，那些可以返回任何
order that they want if one is slow and
如果他们很慢则命令他们想要
three is fast that's okay that three can
三个很快就可以了，三个可以
come back because rather than saying the
回来是因为，而不是说
way I know what you are responding to is
我知道你在回应什么
because you are coming back first and
因为你先回来
then you are coming back second you've
那你就回来了
actually tagged
实际标记
both the requests outbound and the
出站请求和
response inbound and it says hey three
响应入站，它说嘿三
is coming back now go do whatever you
现在回来了，随便你做什么
need to do or three one comes back a
需要做的或三个一个回来
little bit later and says hey go do what
过了一会儿，说嘿去做什么
you need to do there and this is really
您需要在那里做，这确实是
great this has really influenced a lot
太好了，这确实影响了很多
of my thinking especially around RTD BC
我的想法，尤其是关于RTD BC
so we've like asked the database drivers
所以我们想问一下数据库驱动程序
they say hey you know how everybody can
他们说嘿，你知道每个人都可以
only get like four connections to your
只有四个连接到您的
database or eight connections to your
数据库或与您的八个连接
database why don't you have them have
数据库为什么你没有他们有
one connection to your database and then
一个连接到您的数据库，然后
they can have a million streams across
他们可以拥有一百万个流
it as much sort of logical behavior as
它与逻辑行为一样多
they want to on those things and for
他们想在那些东西上
example the Postgres team is starting to
例如Postgres团队开始
look into this idea this as far as
一直研究这个想法
scalability goes is like one of the most
可扩展性就好像是其中之一
amazing things you'll ever see that came
您将看到的奇妙事物来了
out or that is you know sort of integral
还是那是你知道的一种整体
to to our socket here the the protocol
到我们的插座这里的协议
is also bi-directional this has some
也是双向的，这有一些
really interesting use cases so many
真的非常有趣的用例
protocols specifically not TCP have the
专门不是TCP的协议具有
distinction between a client and a
客户与客户之间的区别
server for the lifetime of a connection
连接生命周期内的服务器
so if your HTTP clients write like a web
因此，如果您的HTTP客户端写得像网络
browser you can make a request to a
浏览器，您可以向
server HTTP server and it may respond to
服务器HTTP服务器，它可能会响应
you and that's it right like that's the
你，就是这样，就像
only way data can ever be transmitted
只有这样才能传输数据
right one side initiates all requests
右侧发起所有请求
one side initiates all responses even
一侧甚至会发起所有响应
something like HTTP two which nominally
像HTTP 2这样的东西
is supposed to be it is for example
应该是这样的
multiplex oh yeah there even something
多重哦，是的，甚至有东西
like HTTP two doesn't fully drop that
像HTTP 2一样不能完全删除
distinction right there is sort of a
区分权有一种
mechanism for data to be sent from the
从...发送数据的机制
server to the client or data a bit but
服务器到客户端或数据有点，但
servers can't start an unrequested
服务器无法启动未请求的
stream clients basically have to say
流客户基本上不得不说
okay I'm ready to listen for you to
好吧，我准备好听你的
start sending me some stuff so they've
开始向我发送一些东西，所以他们已经
effectively initiated like half
有效启动了一半
initiated an interaction there so what
在那开始了互动
we what we say with our socket is that
我们用插座说的是
once a client initiates a connection to
客户端启动与
a server right so in our analogy web
服务器正确，所以在我们的类比网络中
browser connects out to our server both
浏览器都连接到我们的服务器
partners we basically lose the
合作伙伴，我们基本上失去了
distinction there was a discussion in
区别在于有一个讨论
the company slack the other day where we
那天公司闲散
were trying to explain this to some
试图向一些人解释
people it's a really hard concept to
人们这是一个很难的概念
grok server and client disappear
grok服务器和客户端消失
both peers are now equivalent to one
现在两个同伴都等于一个
another
另一个
within this network connection either
在此网络连接中
side can initiate a request to the other
一方可以向对方发起请求
side either side can initiate a response
双方都可以发起回应
both of them are really equivalent and
他们两个都是等效的
this is a really interesting side effect
这是一个非常有趣的副作用
when it comes to security specifically
当涉及到安全性时
imagine a router sitting in the middle
想象一个坐在中间的路由器
of a bunch of different clients all
一堆不同的客户
inside of containers today my work on
今天我在容器内工作
Cloud Foundry tells me that the biggest
Cloud Foundry告诉我最大的
possibility of compromise of a container
容器受损的可能性
in a cloud environment is you've got an
在云环境中，您有一个
HTTP port coming in somebody gets on to
有人进入的HTTP端口
that port and exploits something inside
该端口并利用内部的某些东西
of your container now what if you could
现在，如果可以的话
say instead that your container had no
相反说你的容器没有
ingress ports at all there was no way
根本没有入口
into it only outbound connections could
只有出站连接才能进入
be made our socket enables this kind of
使我们的插座启用这种
pattern where all our sockets connect
我们所有的插座连接的模式
out to some trusted party but once
到某个可信任的聚会，但是一次
they're in there any sort of startup
他们在那里任何形式的创业
anybody can request anybody can respond
任何人都可以要求任何人都可以回应
in any network configuration that you
在您所配置的任何网络中
want from there and it gives you
从那里想要，它给你
actually this really interesting
其实这真的很有趣
security posture because of it I think
因此，我认为安全态势
the final set of words that were on
最后的一组词
there was reactive streams backpressure
有反应流反压
Network protocols HTTP we're just gonna
我们将要使用的网络协议HTTP
keep banging on it this entire time
一直都在敲它
generally send a single request as I
通常像我一样发送单个请求
said we all know what this looks like
说我们都知道这是什么样子
returns some sort of arbitrary 10
返回某种任意的10
million lines of JSON back to us there's
一百万行JSON返回给我们
nothing to stop a responder or even
没有什么可以阻止响应者甚至
potentially a requester from going nuts
可能是发疯的请求者
on the server right some huge amount of
在服务器上，大量的
data you are protected a bit by TCP back
TCP返回保护您的数据
pressure this idea that the TCP stacks
压力这个想法，TCP堆栈
are dropped way way down like level to
像水平一样下降到
kind of stack right has these idea of
那种堆叠权有这些想法
queues right until there's you know a
一直排队直到知道
syn ACK pairing kind of thing as data is
syn ACK配对就像数据一样
sent all the way at that low TCP level
一直以较低的TCP级别发送
more data isn't going to be sent you
不会发送更多数据给您
can't blow up the network stack of a
不能炸毁一个
modern computer but what ends up
现代计算机，但最终
happening is you end up with huge queues
发生的事情是你最终排成一列
of on unprocessed data or untransferable
的未处理数据或不可传输
you get a bunch of data sitting in a TCP
您将一堆数据放在TCP中
queue that hasn't made it back up to the
尚未备份到的队列
application and over on the sending side
应用程序以及发送方
you're going to end up with a bunch of
你最终会得到一堆
queues that haven't been able to get
无法获得的队列
across the wire yet and this is really
穿过电线，这确实是
problematic simply because if you have a
有问题只是因为如果你有一个
lot of connections with a lot of full
大量的人脉关系
queues it requires a whole lot
排队需要很多
memory and this is really bad so
内存，这真的很糟糕，所以
reactive streams back pressure here
反应流在这里背压
ensures that we only materialize data
确保我们仅实现数据
and transfer that data when the receiver
并在接收方传输数据时
is ready to process at the receiver
准备在接收方处理
literally sends one of those messages
从字面上发送这些消息之一
one of those frames across the wire and
电线上的那些框架之一，
says okay you're now allowed to send me
说好吧，现在您可以发送给我
the next 128 messages you're now allowed
现在允许您再发送128条消息
to send me the next 64 messages and
给我发送下64条消息，
that's a signal to the server side that
这是向服务器端发出的信号
it can go to a database and read those
它可以进入数据库并读取那些
off disk or go to another micro service
离开磁盘或转到另一个微服务
and go grab some more data materialize
并获取更多数据
it and send it along don't materialize
它并发送它不会实现
it before I can handle it and that is
在我能处理它之前，那就是
actually good for you as well you for
其实对你也有好处
the server so let's take a look at
服务器，让我们看一下
interaction models the first interaction
互动为第一次互动建模
model we said there are four of these
我们说的模型有四个
right the first interaction model that
对第一个交互模型
we always talk about is request response
我们经常谈论的是请求响应
the idea of I want to request an account
我想申请一个账户的想法
number are sorry I'm a banking app sorry
抱歉，我是银行应用程序
let's let's give that I'm a banking app
让我们让我说我是银行应用
right and I'm looking at it and the
对的，我正在看它，
first thing I do is I log in and it's
我要做的第一件事就是登录
gonna show me a splash screen and so it
要给我看一个启动画面，所以
knows my account number it makes a
知道我的帐号后，
request and says hey go find me exactly
要求并说嘿，去找我
what the balance is for this particular
这个特殊的平衡是什么
account number standard request response
帐号标准请求响应
semantics we see the line all the way up
语义，我们一直看到这条线
there at the top so it was a mistake
在顶部，所以这是一个错误
given how short I am client requests
考虑到我要求客户的时间有多短
response you pass in a request payload
您传递请求有效负载的响应
just a single object right whatever it
只是单个对象而已
is let's call it the account number in
我们称它为帐号
this particular case and you get one of
这个特殊的情况，你会得到
these mono payloads back right for those
这些单声道有效载荷适合那些
who've missed it some of my other talks
谁错过了我的其他一些演讲
all of this stuff anytime you're gonna
所有这些东西，只要你要
see me do a demo up here our socket
看到我在这里做一个演示我们的插座
especially is based on project reactor
特别是基于项目反应堆
which is sort of the spring affiliated
这是 Spring 附属的
implementation of reactive programming
反应式编程的实现
there are other alternatives there are
还有其他选择
other languages but fundamentally we
其他语言，但从根本上讲，我们
have two main types in project reactor
项目反应堆有两种主要类型
we have the idea of a flux which is a
我们有一个通量的想法
stream of 0 to n things that will come
从0到n的事物流
back to us element element element
回到我们的元素element element
element and a mono which means either 0
元素和一个单声道，表示0
or 1 of these things are going to come
或这些事情之一
back to us so in this case we say we're
回到我们身边，所以在这种情况下，我们说我们
going to send you a response we expect
我们希望能给您答复
one payload to come back now this is
一个有效载荷现在返回
almost certainly exactly what you do we
几乎可以肯定您在做什么
have been so brainwashed into
被洗脑了
doing request/response from HTTP and
从HTTP执行请求/响应
realistically most of the information we
实际上，我们提供的大多数信息
want to know is a request response kind
想知道是一种请求响应类型
of interaction so nothing wrong with
互动，所以没有错
this but even this something that you
这个，但即使这个东西，你
know you can do today in HTTP it
知道你今天可以用HTTP做它
surpasses HTTP because it's asynchronous
超越HTTP，因为它是异步的
and multiplexed we need a single
和多路传输，我们需要一个
connection where I can just send a
连接，我可以发送一个
million request response calls and get
百万请求响应电话并获得
them all back in a jumbled order as fast
他们都以混乱的速度快回来了
as they can be processed on the other
因为它们可以在另一个上进行处理
side something you cannot do today with
支持您今天无法做的事情
HTTP the next one is sort of an
HTTP，下一个是
optimization of request response we call
我们称之为请求响应的优化
this fire-and-forget which is a very I
这就是我忘了
don't know it's a very American thing to
不知道这是非常美国的事情
say certainly I'm not sure if it has a
说当然，我不确定它是否有
great translation on the other side with
另一边的翻译很棒
our gun culture this time we see a mano
这次我们的枪支文化我们看到了一个马诺
void right and a mano void is sort of a
无效的权利和马诺无效的有点
special idiom in the reactive world and
反应世界中的特殊习语和
this basically says hey I'm not actually
这基本上是说我不是
waiting for a response you're not good
等待回应你不好
you're always gonna send to me zero
你总是会寄给我零
because void is not a type that you can
因为void不是您可以使用的类型
instantiate and Java so all I want you
实例化和Java，所以我想要你
to do is signal to me as soon as you're
要做的就是向我发出信号
done so when we say find and forget
当我们说找到并忘记
sorry fire and forget we want to send
对不起火，忘了我们要发送
you a payload and I don't care right
你是有效载荷，我不在乎
like it's gonna get there the TCP stack
就像它将到达那里的TCP堆栈
will guarantee the payload got there but
将保证有效载荷到达那里，但是
you don't need to tell me you got it you
你不需要告诉我你懂了
don't need to tell me you're done it's
不需要告诉我您已经完成了
just gonna go over the wire and I'm
只是要越过电线，我
gonna go on with my life there are
要继续我的生活
significant efficiencies for this mostly
这主要是显着的效率
on the networking thing imagine a
关于网络的事情想象一个
scenario where I sent you what do I have
我寄给你的情况我有什么
here non-critical event logging right
这里非关键事件记录正确
I'm gonna send you a log line and maybe
我要给您发送一条日志行，也许
you need to sync that log line into a
您需要将该日志行同步到
database well realistically that's gonna
现实的数据库将
you know to take into database gonna
你知道要进入数据库
have to wait on the connection pool to
必须在连接池上等待
get it gonna have to wait for the insert
得到它必须等待插入
and the commit that follows it after the
以及之后的提交
database writing to the disk it may be
数据库写入磁盘可能是
half a second before you can get back to
半秒钟后您才能返回
me and say hey this was all done but if
我说，嘿，这一切都完成了，但是如果
I don't care right event logging isn't
我不在乎正确的事件记录不是
particularly critical then why don't I
特别关键，那我为什么不
just say hey here's a piece of data and
只是说嘿，这是一条数据，
you can release it immediately
您可以立即释放它
you'll go on with your life you'll still
你会继续你的生活
try and get a database connection you'll
尝试获得数据库连接
still try and sink a disk so still right
仍然尝试使磁盘下沉，因此仍然正确
but you've released a network connection
但您已释放网络连接
or logical connection from your side I
或逻辑上的联系
can go on with my life without having to
可以继续我的生活而不必
wait around for you to come back and
等你回来
tell me that you're done on the four
告诉我你已经完成了四个
sort of less trivial kind of stuff
一种不太琐碎的东西
client-server processing you know the
客户服务器处理您知道
key thing here is to make sure that
这里的关键是要确保
we're releasing these kinds of resources
我们正在释放这些资源
as quickly as we can especially in sort
尽我们所能尽快
of non blocking high efficiency kind of
无阻塞高效的
environments so the next interaction
环境，以便下次互动
model is request stream the example we
模型是请求流的例子，我们
have here is again request with an
再次在这里有一个请求
account number and I want you to then
帐号，然后我想让你
give me a real-time stream of all of my
给我我所有的实时流
account transactions literally not the
帐户交易实际上不是
ones that have already happened but as
已经发生但
I'm standing here and my brother's over
我站在这里，我哥哥已经过去了
there and he's got a credit card and he
在那里，他有一张信用卡，他
goes and swipes it to get a coffee or
去刷卡喝咖啡或
something like that it can show up in my
这样的东西可以出现在我的
app right this happens in quite a number
应用正确，这种情况发生的次数很多
of sort of modern especially credit card
现代的特别是信用卡
apps really like to do this kind of
应用程序真的很喜欢这样做
thing what we end up seeing here is when
我们最终在这里看到的是什么时候
we go and call request stream with that
我们去呼叫请求流
same payload this time we don't get a
这次相同的有效载荷我们没有得到
mano back we get a flux back instead we
马诺回来，我们得到一个通量反而我们
are going to get a stream of these
将会得到这些
events and maybe the first thing that
事件，也许第一件事
shows up is all of the the transactions
显示所有交易
that have happened over the last hour
在过去一个小时内发生的
the last two hours but we don't signal
最近两个小时，但我们不发信号
that this stream is complete all right
这个流是完整的好吧
that's just the first bit of it gets
那只是它的第一步
written on my my app and now every once
写在我的应用程序上，现在每一次
in a while another thing comes across us
一会儿我们又遇到另一件事
we're still listening just waiting for
我们还在听，只是在等待
it and that gets written in right so
它并以正确的方式编写，因此
it's analogous to a request response
这类似于请求响应
where it returns a collection except
返回集合的地方
each element comes in alone because it's
每个元素单独进入是因为
effectively a never-ending collection
有效地永无止境的收藏
one of the key things here this is the
这里的关键之一是
first interaction model we've that we're
我们拥有的第一个互动模型
taking a look at where requests end
看看请求在哪里结束
semantics which is what we call sort of
所谓的语义
reactive back pressure and the reason we
反应背压以及我们的原因
call it that is the way this works is
称之为工作方式是
you do a subscription so you basically
您进行订阅，因此您基本上
say hey publisher we're all ready to go
说嘿发布者，我们都准备好了
yep everything's ready okay requests for
是的，一切准备就绪，可以要求
requests eight requests and effectively
有效地请求八个请求
and that's how we sing signal to the
这就是我们向
publisher to send me data so the key
发布者向我发送数据，所以关键
thing here once again is suppose that
这里的事情再次是假设
very first thing we say okay go get me
我们说的第一件事，好的，去救我
the first hundred and twenty eight but
前一百二十八，但是
there's actually ten thousand things
实际上有一万件事
that have happened in the last hour
最近一小时发生的
right it can't send me that ten thousand
是的，它不能寄给我一万
it's not materialized not ready to send
它尚未实现，不准备发送
all of a sudden I start seeing you know
突然我开始看到你知道
a ton of data coming in on my phone like
大量数据通过手机进入
oh no cancel right maybe it only got
哦，没有取消权，也许只有
halfway through that ten thousand that
一万的一半
it needed materialized it didn't have to
它需要实现，而不必
spin the disks underneath
旋转下面的磁盘
database to get all of that data up so
数据库来获取所有这些数据
there is huge performance improvements
有巨大的性能改进
that you see from this and this is one
您从中看到的，这是一个
of the the really interesting things the
真正有趣的事情
the original author of this this
这个的原始作者
particular protocol are one of the
特定协议是以下之一
original authors I should say eventually
最终我应该说的原始作者
went to work and took this with him at
去上班并带他去了
Facebook and the key thing that they
Facebook及其关键之处
were looking for at Facebook was that
在寻找Facebook是
kind of efficiency we're going to talk
我们要谈的效率
about a ton of other you know sort of
大约一吨你知道的其他
improvements that you're going to see on
您将看到的改进
this as the as the talk goes on but they
随着谈话的进行，但是他们
really were interested in this idea that
对这个想法真的很感兴趣
they don't have to materialize a bunch
他们不必实现一大堆
of data that will never get to customers
永远不会获得客户的数据
at you know sort of at a scale of
在你所知道的范围内
something like Facebook this has
像Facebook这样的东西
material dollar value think of you know
物质美元价值想起你知道
how many applications how many phone
多少个应用程序多少个电话
apps are currently running and connected
应用目前正在运行并已连接
to Facebook at any given time actually
实际上在任何给定时间到Facebook
makes a really really significant
真的很重要
difference so the final interaction
差异，因此最终互动
model that we're going to take a look at
我们将要研究的模型
here is channel the example I have here
这是频道我在这里的例子
is incredibly contrived like I must have
像我必须做的那样难以置信
spent 10 minutes trying to figure out
花了十分钟试图弄清楚
something it is request something with
它要求的东西
an account number you're going to
您要使用的帐号
respond with that real-time stream of
以实时的
account transactions but then I press a
帐户交易，但随后我按
filter button and that filter button
筛选器按钮和那个筛选器按钮
says I only want you to show me the ones
说我只想让你给我看
that are for coffee and so then it goes
那是喝咖啡的，然后它就走了
and enumerates a whole different list
并列举了一个完整的列表
and then my brother next to me right
然后我哥哥在我旁边
here goes and buys a coffee and that is
去买咖啡，那就是
the only thing that shows up right
唯一显示正确的东西
really contract I am sure there are no
真的签合同，我确定没有
apps that actually do this but the key
真正做到这一点的应用程序，但关键
thing here is well we see the flux
这里的事情很好，我们看到了变化
payload coming out we'd expect that sort
有效载荷出来，我们希望那种
of stream of data but we also have a
数据流，但我们还有一个
flux payload going in and those could be
通量有效载荷进入，那些可能是
two different kinds of payloads I don't
两种不同类型的有效载荷
have to be symmetric and what this
必须对称，这是什么
basically is is I want you to open a
基本上是我要你开一个
pipe and I'm just gonna send some
管道，我只是要发送一些
messages sometimes and you're just gonna
有时会有消息，而你只是
send us a message sometimes and you can
有时给我们发送消息，您可以
do anything you want and if you really
做任何你想做的事情，如果你真的
think about it the unstructured channel
考虑一下非结构化渠道
allows any arbitrary interaction model
允许任何任意的交互模型
like if you don't like the other three
就像你不喜欢其他三个
interaction models plus this one you can
互动模型以及这一模型
implement anything that you want I get
实现我想要的任何东西
to send one and you only get to send two
发送一个，而您只能发送两个
I get to send two you only get to send
我要发送两个，你只能发送
one it doesn't matter realistically but
一，实际上并不重要，但是
the key is that if you can sort of think
关键是，如果您可以思考
of this is the the bailout you can
这就是您可以进行的救助
actually implement all of the other
实际上实现所有其他
interaction models on top of the channel
渠道顶部的互动模型
may
可以
if you wanted to but we sort of promote
如果您愿意，但我们可以促进
those to be the other three to be
那些要成为其他三个
first-class kinds of things okay so
一流的东西好吗
that's a lot of stuff how's everybody
很多东西大家好
doing okay so let's take a look at some
做得很好，让我们来看一些
code you'll be really happy to know the
代码，您将非常高兴知道
later bits of this demo we're done right
本演示的后续部分，我们做对了
around ten minutes before they started I
他们开始前十分钟左右
was over with the boot team taking a
启动团队结束了一次
look at the very newest stuff actually
看看实际上最新的东西
that they've they've put into place so
他们已经把它们放到位，所以
what does our socket actually look like
我们的插座实际上是什么样的
nope this is the wrong one that's not a
不，这是错误的，不是
great sign actually Oh No okay I got it
很好的信号哦，不，我知道了
I know where I am now okay so our socket
我知道我现在可以在哪里，所以我们的插座
itself starts the the key thing that you
本身启动了关键的事情
end up with is this idea of an our
最后就是我们的想法
socket factory and our socket factory is
插座工厂，我们的插座工厂是
used then to create either a server or a
然后用于创建服务器或服务器
client one of the key principles of the
客户的主要原则之一
our socket API is that it is perfectly
我们的套接字API是完美的
symmetrical okay there is this thing
对称还好，有这个东西
called in our socket our socket
在我们的插座中称为插座
if I can do it like that
如果我能那样做
our socket has request/response
我们的套接字有请求/响应
fire-and-forget request channel request
即弃请求通道请求
stream on it now think of this if you
现在就在它上面流，如果你
were an implementer the key takeaway
是实施者的主要收获
from this is that if I'm a server I need
这是因为如果我是服务器，我需要
to implement all of those methods
实现所有这些方法
something around me will call into those
我周围的东西会呼唤那些
and I will honor them and respond them
我会尊重他们并回应他们
out but with that perfect symmetry it
但具有完美的对称性
means that if I'm a client something
表示如果我是客户
that has implemented this gets to be
已经实现了这一点
handed to me and I call one of those
递给我，我称其中之一
methods and get the response back from
方法并从中获取响应
whatever that is this means that you can
不管这意味着你可以
do an implementation one of the we'll
做一个我们将要执行的工作
talk about Network transports in a
谈论网络传输
second one of the network transports is
网络传输的第二个是
simply there is a single object and you
只是有一个物体而你
talk one method to another method and it
讲一种方法和另一种方法
just goes through this interface you
只是通过这个界面你
don't really know what happens but this
真的不知道会发生什么，但这
gives us this great ability to sort of
赋予我们这种强大的能力
have a symmetry and an ease of
具有对称性和易用性
understanding an ease of implementation
了解易于实施
between these things okay
这些东西之间还好
so in this particular case we're going
所以在这种情况下，我们要
to set up a server by receiving we're
通过接收我们来设置服务器
going to put in our socket
放入我们的插座
implementation into it and we're going
实施到它，我们要去
to say that we're going to use WebSocket
说我们将使用WebSocket
as a transport we'll talk about that a
作为交通工具，我们将讨论
little bit later on and we start this
稍后，我们开始
guy up and what ends up happening is
家伙起来，最终发生的是
that at some point someone will make a
在某个时候某人会做出
call passing in us in a payload we're
呼叫在有效载荷中传递给我们
down at a really low level we deal a lot
下降到非常低的水平，我们处理了很多
with byte buffers at this particular
在这个特定的字节缓冲区
juncture and this payloads going to have
关键时刻，这些有效载荷将具有
a number inside of it so we're going to
里面有一个数字，所以我们要
parse out the number that was in it
解析出其中的数字
we'll go ahead and say hey we receive
我们会继续说，嘿，我们收到了
this number right here and then we're
这个号码在这里，然后我们
going to generate a bunch of responses
将产生一堆回应
in the other direction right in this
在另一个方向上
particular case because we're doing a
特殊情况，因为我们正在做
request stream one in and out and so in
请求流一进一出等
this case we're going to say okay if you
在这种情况下，如果您愿意，我们会说好的
send me one I'm gonna give you from zero
给我一个，我将从零开始给你
to one if you send me two I'm gonna give
如果你给我两个我要给
you zero one two if you send me ten I'm
你零一二如果你寄给我十我是
gonna give you zero one three we're
要给你零一三我们
gonna send all of that data back out to
会将所有数据发送回
you and we just simply map it back into
您和我们只是将其映射回
string dot value of
的字符串点值
so what does the client look like well
那客户看起来怎么样
we see that symmetry in action again our
我们再次看到行动中的对称性
socket client Factory
套接字客户端工厂
we're gonna go ahead and connect this
我们将继续进行连接
time we're gonna make an outbound
我们要出站的时间
connection over the web client transport
通过Web客户端传输进行连接
and in this particular case we're gonna
在这种情况下，我们将
say okay I want to send out my requests
说好，我想发送我的请求
are going to go out between 0 and 10
会在0到10之间熄灭
will create one of those payloads here
将在此处创建这些有效载荷之一
and we're gonna call our socket request
我们将调用我们的套接字请求
stream right now imagine then that
现在想像一下
symmetry
对称
our socket request stream passing in my
我们的套接字请求流传入
message is quite a lot like calling our
信息很像打电话给我们
socket request stream right here right
套接字请求流就在这里
we just have the other half of that
我们只有那一半
symmetric interaction and then once it
对称互动，然后一旦
sends us out a bunch of data right we
向我们发送了很多数据
did this flat mappy thing here which
在这里做了平坦的罂粟花
basically says ok request stream is
基本上说好的请求流是
gonna hand me a stream of data coming
会递给我一系列数据
back when I send one it's going to send
返回当我发送一个它将要发送
me 0 and 1 when it's in when I send 2
当我发送2时我0和1
it's gonna send me 0 1 2 and then 0 1 3
它会寄给我0 1 2然后0 1 3
all the way up to 10 in theory and we'll
从理论上一直上升到10
wait for that to finish so let's go
等待那完成，让我们开始吧
ahead and start the server
提前启动服务器
every night
每天晚上
yeah okay I think that's running been
是的，我想这已经
doing so well on demos it's only a
在演示上做得很好，只是一个
matter of time till it fails on me here
时间问题，直到它在我这里失败
so what do we see here we managed to
所以我们在这里看到了什么
send out a whole bunch of data 0 1 2 3 4
发送大量数据0 1 2 3 4
5 6 7 8 9
5 6 7 8 9
remember there's only a single
记住只有一个
connection at 80 81 all of these things
在80 81连接所有这些东西
got to go out but now all of a sudden I
必须出去，但突然之间我
see a bunch of processing coming in and
看到一堆处理程序进入
all sorts of random ordering especially
各种随机排序，尤其是
when we start getting down here and how
当我们开始在这里下车以及如何
often these come back there is no
通常这些回来没有
guarantee of order we see the server
订单保证，我们看到服务器
side of this receiving a bunch of stuff
这边收到一堆东西
it received two different things before
之前有两件事
it started sending things back out so
它开始发送东西回来，所以
ordering doesn't actually matter right
排序实际上并不重要
effectively every single time we're all
每次我们都有效
server we're going to hear every single
服务器，我们将听到每一个
time a new request comes here we re
当一个新的请求来到这里我们
execute this in a completely non
完全不执行
blocking manner if we did sort of a
如果我们做了某种
thread sleep for some random period time
线程睡眠一段时间
that'd be okay all of these are sort of
没关系，所有这些都是
in flight simultaneously and it's all
同时在飞行中
around this idea of a request stream if
围绕这个请求流的想法，如果
I wanted to do one of the request
我想做一个要求
responses you can instead say hey
您可以反而说嘿
request response I'm gonna implement
请求答复我要实施
that in some way where I get a payload
以某种方式我得到了有效载荷
and I return a mono payload back I do
然后我返回单声道有效载荷
some sort of transformation maybe I go
某种转变也许我会去
to a database and do some kind of query
到数据库并进行某种查询
something like that
这样的东西
okay
好的
so let's talk a little bit more about
所以让我们多谈一点
interesting things beyond just a
有趣的事情不仅仅是
programming model of our socket or
我们套接字的编程模型或
socket it turns out and this is the
插座事实证明，这是
thing I think that really attracted me
我认为这真的吸引了我
to the project and said okay I want to
参加该项目，然后说我想
actually become a committer on this
实际上成为这个的提交者
particular thing I want to be there and
我想在那里的特殊事物
and be a proponent of this is that our
对此的支持者是
socket is crazily one of the most
套接字是最疯狂的套接字之一
flexible protocols around it's
灵活的协议
completely language agnostic right it's
完全不可知的语言是
defined in terms of frames transfer
根据帧传输定义
binary frames transferred over a network
通过网络传输的二进制帧
which means that we already have
这意味着我们已经有
implementations in Java and C++ are
Java和C ++中的实现是
probably the most mature Java
可能是最成熟的Java
specifically because of Netflix and the
特别是因为Netflix和
association with the spring team C++
与春季团队C ++的联系
happens to be the language to jour for a
碰巧是一种旅行的语言
Facebook JavaScript because everybody
Facebook JavaScript，因为所有人
wants to do this inside of a web browser
想要在网络浏览器中执行此操作
Kotlin go and there are many many more
Kotlin走了，还有更多
so in addition to being language
所以除了是语言
agnostic it's also payload agnostic
不可知的，它也是不可知的
we're gonna see some sending of
我们会看到一些发送
protobufs I personally would always send
我个人会一直发送的protobuf
Jason but if you're more into C bore
杰森，但如果您更喜欢C
some custom binary kind of protocol
一些自定义的二进制协议
because you're pushing down towards
因为你正朝着
efficiency as much as you can sure send
您可以肯定地发送的效率
any payload you want it's not like
您想要的任何有效负载都不是
something like G RPC which more or less
像G RPC之类的东西
is you must send protobufs and nothing
你必须发送protobufs什么都没有
else and then finally it's transport
否则最后就是运输
agnostic as well this turns out to be
不可知的也是
really really key because it allows you
真的很关键，因为它可以让您
to go over TCP where you can so
在可以的地方通过TCP
typically inside of a data center going
通常在数据中心内部
over TCP without the overhead of the
通过TCP，而没有
framing of something like WebSockets or
像WebSockets或
HTTP is probably the most efficient way
HTTP可能是最有效的方法
you'll actually be able to transfer data
您实际上将能够传输数据
across a network WebSockets though exist
跨网络WebSockets虽然存在
for situations where you don't have that
对于您没有的情况
say your phone over the open Internet to
在开放的互联网上说您的电话
whatever your edge server is in the
无论您的边缘服务器位于
cloud you can use HTTP 2 which gets a
云，您可以使用HTTP 2获得
little bit more efficient because we can
因为我们可以提高效率
sort of piggyback on the the
有点背piggy式
multiplexing of HTTP 2 and if you are
HTTP 2的多路传输，如果您
insane and in the finance industry those
疯狂和金融业中的那些
two things go together quite a lot you
两件事在一起很多
can use the Aeron protocol which is this
可以使用Aeron协议
ultra high speed UDP guaranteed delivery
超高速UDP保证交付
with symmetric bla bla bla don't know
与对称bla bla bla不知道
it's apparently the fastest possible
这显然是最快的
thing but given that TCP we regularly
事情，但鉴于TCP，我们经常
see like 60,000 requests per second over
每秒看到60,000个请求
it this seems really like a lot over
这似乎真的结束了很多
call overkill right
称呼过度杀伤权
but if we say that it's flexible how
但是如果我们说它很灵活，
flexible is it how flexible is it what
灵活吗？
if I told you that switching from
如果我告诉你从
WebSocket which we said isn't the most
我们说过的WebSocket最多
efficient way to transfer data we said
我们所说的有效的数据传输方式
yeah okay
好的
I just wanna use TCP instead this
我只是想用TCP代替
pluggable layer underneath because the
因为下面的可插拔层
frame is all about a binary encapsulated
框架都是关于二进制封装的
message that needs to be sent from point
需要从点发送的消息
A to point B the fact that it's sent
A指向B事实已发送
over TCP doesn't matter to any bit of
通过TCP无关紧要
the network stack after that
之后的网络堆栈
do the same thing on the other side
在另一边做同样的事情
and we see one little one down there
我们在那边看到一个小人
received eight data has been sent didn't
收到八个数据已发送未
effect almost anything certainly didn't
效果几乎没有
affect any of our program right any of
影响我们的任何计划权利
our actual application code barely even
我们的实际应用程序代码几乎没有
affected the configuration here we could
影响了这里的配置，我们可以
have put in HTTP two we could have put
放了两个我们本来可以放的HTTP
an Aeron really really easy to get
Aeron真的很容易得到
portability but one of the really key
可移植性，但真正的关键之一
things is it's quite likely if you
事情是很有可能的，如果你
really adopt our socket it's an a
真的采用了我们的插座
heterogeneous environment you're likely
您可能会在异构环境中
internally server to server within a
内部服务器到服务器
data center to use TCP externally
数据中心在外部使用TCP
between devices and your edge server
在设备和边缘服务器之间
you're gonna use something like
您将使用类似
WebSockets or h2 but you never have to
WebSockets或h2，但您不必
learn a new programming model it's
学习一个新的编程模型
simply a configuration choice that you
只是您的配置选择
have to make that's a really really
必须使这真的是真的
important bit of flexibility again to
重要的灵活性再次
poke at that other protocol h2 or buses
戳其他协议h2或总线
right so safe harbor statement basically
对，所以基本上安全港声明
says everything I'm about to show you
说我要告诉你的一切
could be a lie we don't know yet
可能是我们还不知道的谎言
so in some other kinds of flexibility
所以其他一些灵活性
for our socket it's programming model
对于我们的套接字，它是编程模型
agnostic right the our socket interface
与我们的套接字接口无关
is serviceable programming model but not
是可用的编程模型，但不是
great it's designed to be a building
很棒，它被设计成一栋建筑
block starting to hear a theme in my
阻止开始听到我的主题
talks right artoo DBC designed to be a
谈论正确的artoo DBC设计为
building blocks not a humane API people
构件不是人性化的API人员
don't use this right this our socket
不要在我们的插座上使用此权限
interface is a very very similar way you
界面与您非常相似
can use it like the code wasn't the
可以像代码不是那样使用它
worst code I've ever seen but
我见过的最糟糕的代码，但是
realistically you as an upper level high
实际上，您是高层次的
abstraction application developer wants
开发人员想要的抽象应用程序
something different maybe you want RPC
有些不同，也许您想要RPC
maybe you want messaging style so let's
也许您想要消息传递样式，所以让我们
take a look at some other opportunities
看看其他机会
there
那里
so I said boo hiss on G RPC but I get it
所以我对G RPC说嘘声嘘声，但我明白了
like I get RPC I am actually old enough
就像我得到RPC一样，我实际上已经够老了
I remember the last time RPC failed like
我记得上一次RPC失败像
in the late 90s early 2000s because of
在90年代末2000年代初，由于
all the tight coupling but this is the
所有的紧密耦合，但这是
industry we're in we get to do it again
我们所处的行业，我们必须再次做
we get to fail at it again it's gonna be
我们将再次失败
amazing
惊人
so you're the kind of person who really
所以你是那种真正的人
likes RPC interaction models and you
喜欢RPC交互模型，而您
really like making sure that all your
非常喜欢确保您所有的
clients and all your servers are
客户端和您所有的服务器都是
absolutely always locked in sync with
绝对总是与同步
zero compatibility problems yep great
零兼容性问题
probably also people who use mono repos
可能也是使用mono仓库的人
I don't get it
我不明白
let's define a service right a simple
让我们定义一个简单的服务吧
service request extrema values request
服务请求极值请求
another stream of values we define what
我们定义了另一种价值流
the message request comes in what the
消息请求来自
message response goes back out this is
消息响应回退这是
sort of straightforward protobuf or
一种简单的protobuf或
sorry IDL style configuration this we
对不起IDL样式配置这个我们
compile down into a protobuf we inject
编译成我们注入的protobuf
some are socket RPC goodness that sits
有些是套接字RPC优点
behind it so that on your server you
在它后面，以便在您的服务器上
have one of these simple service things
拥有这些简单的服务之一
which actually it's not the worst
实际上这不是最坏的
protobuf code i've ever seen but it has
我见过的protobuf代码，但它有
our two methods request of another
我们两种方法的另一个要求
stream of values request to be stream of
值流请求成为
values takes in a simple request as a
值接受一个简单的请求作为
payload simple request and some payloads
有效负载简单请求和一些有效负载
from there which means then that we can
从那里，这意味着我们可以
simply implement this right here's that
简单地实现这个权利就是
request stream of values that is sort of
请求某种类型的值流
a an RPC style really highly
真正的RPC风格
contextualized very semantically
非常语义化的上下文
understandable kind of API returns a
易于理解的API返回
fluxes simple responses takes in a
通量简单的响应需要
simple request in this case we're gonna
在这种情况下的简单要求
do the exact same thing we're gonna go
做我们要去的完全相同的事情
to the request message pull out whatever
到请求消息中拉出任何东西
the number was from it returned a range
数字是从它返回一个范围
of these things because we are going to
这些事情，因为我们要
return a range of those responses let's
返回这些响应的范围，让我们
go ahead and start this one up I think I
继续并开始这一步，我想我
made sure from now on we're always using
确保从现在开始我们一直在使用
TCP as well but even with this RPC style
TCP也是如此，即使使用这种RPC样式
we could just as easily go through
我们可以轻松地通过
changes to WebSocket or some alternative
更改WebSocket或其他方法
that you see there on the client side
您在客户端看到的
this is great somewhere in the world
这在世界上某个地方很棒
there is one of these simple service
这些简单的服务之一
clients let's take a look at what this
客户让我们看看这是什么
thing does it's got a bit more code in
事情是否有更多的代码
it this time but it looks very very
这次，但是看起来非常非常
symmetrical
对称的
here's request another stream of values
这里要求另一个价值流
takes in a simple request and a bike
接受一个简单的请求和一辆自行车
buff here's request our instead of
要求这里而不是
request another here's request simple
请求另一个这里的请求简单
request and bike button so I can build
请求和自行车按钮，以便我可以建立
all of those things with this sort of
所有这些东西与这种
direct very direct programming model
直接非常直接的编程模型
just start using plans okay
刚开始使用计划就可以了
so I create a new one of these clients
所以我创建了一个新的客户
passing in that our socket client that I
传入我们的套接字客户端
created and that gives me the ability to
创建，这使我有能力
create myself a new simple request and
为自己创建一个新的简单请求，
set what its message is going to be and
设置其消息将是什么，
then make the request request to stream
然后发出请求请求流
of values or request another stream of
值或请求其他流
values if I wanted to go that way
值，如果我想走那条路
instead get nice auto completion this
而是获得很好的自动完成功能
looks like calling any other method the
看起来像调用任何其他方法
fact that it is going over the network
它正在通过网络的事实
is invisible to you
对你不可见
so output once again does pretty much
所以输出再次做了很多
exactly what we wanted to this is a step
这正是我们想要的一步
above the our socket interface right
在我们的套接字接口上方
this is a really good strategy I think
我认为这是一个非常好的策略
we can all agree using the our socket
我们都可以同意使用我们的套接字
interface isn't good even if we disagree
即使我们不同意，界面也不是很好
on RPC so how about a third kind all
在RPC上，那么第三种怎么样
right if you're familiar with spring
对，如果你熟悉 Spring
don't look at that countdown latch there
不要看那倒计时闩锁
this was the bit that we were working on
这就是我们正在努力的一点
right at the end if you're familiar with
如果您熟悉的话，在最后
spring one of the things that we've
Spring 是我们要做的事情之一
always been really really good at is
一直很擅长的是
this idea of allowing you to just write
这个想法让你只写
a method that has some inputs that has
有一些输入的方法
some outputs you can basically choose
您可以基本上选择一些输出
any damn thing you want and whack in an
你想要的任何该死的东西
annotation on it saying hey here's what
上面的注释说嘿这是什么
I want you to do right whether this is
我要你做对
HTTP control or sorry web MVC
HTTP控制或对不起的Web MVC
controllers or web flux controllers or
控制器或卷筒纸流量控制器或
something like that it gives you a
像这样的东西给你
really loose coupling from the things
与事物之间的耦合非常松散
that are going to call you you don't
会打电话给你，你不会
know how it's gonna get there but
知道它将如何到达那里，但是
somebody's gonna somehow say I want to
有人会说我想
send or I want to call a request stream
发送或我想调用请求流
and a pass you a payload I want you to
向您传递有效载荷，我要您
return me a flux
退还给我
once again we do the exact same things
再次，我们做完全一样的事情
that we've always done there with our
我们一直都在那里做着
flux range on the way back out you'll
通量范围在您返回的途中
notice one of the big deals is that
注意，其中一项大交易是
we're not using payload this time spring
Spring 这个时候我们不使用有效载荷
is really good about Auto type can work
关于自动类型真的很不错
coercion as well so we something is
也是强制的，所以我们有一点是
going to convert into a string for us
将为我们转换成字符串
here we'll go ahead and return a string
在这里，我们将继续并返回一个字符串
out it'll return it'll turn it down into
它将返回它将被拒绝
those byte buffs that need to be sent
那些需要发送的字节增益
back across the other side configuration
回到另一边
in this particular case is great I'm
在这种情况下我很棒
using spring boot 2.2 m3 and I did
使用 spring boot 2.2M3，我做了
nothing no that's not true I lied about
没有，不是，那不是真的，我撒谎了
that on the server side I had to do
在服务器端，我必须要做
application properties I had to say that
应用程序属性我不得不说
we're gonna listen on 80 83 for the
我们将在80 83听
spring stuff that was not at all what I
Spring 的东西根本不是我
want to do
想做
server we did a little bit of
服务器，我们做了一点
customization just so it knows how to
定制只是它知道如何
encode and decode strings by default up
默认情况下对字符串进行编码和解码
until about 30 minutes ago when a change
直到大约30分钟前
was committed to spring boot it only
致力于 Spring 引导它只
does see bore and Jason but now it'll do
确实看到了无聊和杰森，但现在它将
spring sorry it'll do strings as well
Spring 对不起，它也会打弦
but easy customization using sort of
但易于使用的自定义方式
standard spring boot kind of ways of
标准 spring boot 的一种方式
doing customization here we'll go ahead
在这里进行定制，我们将继续
and fire this particular thing off and
并解雇这件事
so now what we sudden we have a server
所以现在我们突然有了服务器
that doesn't implement an interface
没有实现接口
directly so it can be a bit more
直接，这样可以多一点
flexible all it knows is someone's
灵活地知道某人的
asking me to route to request stream it
要求我路由以请求流式传输
wants to send me a string based payload
想向我发送基于字符串的有效载荷
I want to send a bunch of string based
我想发送一串基于
payloads back in the other direction we
有效载荷朝着另一个方向
see that the meteora socket server is
看到meteora套接字服务器是
now running on 8080 three spring client
现在在8080三Spring 客户端上运行
what does it look like to go in the
进去看起来像什么
other direction this isn't actually
另一个方向，这实际上不是
really a spring app but we have this
确实是春季应用，但我们有这个
sort of utility called an our socket
一种叫做我们的套接字的实用程序
requester it wraps the our socket client
请求者包装了我们的套接字客户端
side behavior this is again me setting
副作用这又是我的设置
up some configuration that hopefully you
进行一些配置，希望您
won't need by the time sort of m4 rc1
不需要m4 rc1的时间
comes out but here we get to do this
出来，但在这里我们要做
thing where we get to say hey hey
我们要说的东西嘿嘿
requester go route me a message to
请求者去给我留言
request stream that endpoint that I saw
请求流我看到的那个端点
on the other side I want you to send
在另一边，我要你发送
this data and I want you to go return me
这些数据，我要你去还给我
a flux of strings from that you're gonna
一串串的字符串，你会
this basically translate when you say
当你说这基本上翻译
retrieve flux is effectively it saying
有效地恢复流量是在说
hey execute request stream for me give
嘿执行请求流给我
me a bunch of data back automatically
我会自动返回一堆数据
type cores it into a string and I'll
类型将其插入字符串，然后
fire some more data off I ran this once
发射更多数据我运行了一次
so yeah there we go and it all comes
所以是的，我们去了，一切都来了
back so there are multiple ways because
返回，所以有多种方法，因为
our socket is so flexible it sort of
我们的插座是如此灵活，以至于
sits in this sandwich between a bunch of
坐在这个三明治之间
protocols that doesn't herbs are a bunch
没有草药的协议是一堆
of networked transports it doesn't care
无关的网络传输
about and a bunch of programming models
关于和一堆编程模型
and payloads it doesn't care about
和无关紧要的有效载荷
sitting on top of it it makes it really
坐在它上面使它真的
really flexible
真的很灵活
so you've seen those three raw our
所以你看过这三个原始的
socket RPC style messaging style we are
套接字RPC样式消息传递样式
actually interested I M down on our PC
在我们的PC上对IM真正感兴趣
clearly but I know that the industry has
显然，但我知道该行业已经
a huge preference for it and so we're
非常喜欢它，所以我们
really interested in hearing what you
对听到你的声音很感兴趣
like to do should we focus more energy
我们应该集中精力做些什么
into making our PC bet or should we
进入我们的PC赌注，还是我们应该
focus more energy into the messaging
将更多精力投入到消息传递中
style is there some other kind of
风格还有别的
protocol programming model that you'd
您想要的协议编程模型
like to see that we haven't demonstrated
希望看到我们还没有证明
here talk to the spring team talk to the
在这里与 The Spring Team 交谈
boot team talk to the our soccer team we
足球队与我们的足球队交谈
are really interested in how exactly
真的很感兴趣
you're going to use something like this
你将要使用这样的东西
so we're gonna spend much of the rest of
所以我们要花剩下的大部分时间
this time talking about other features
这次谈论其他功能
that are in the our socket protocol
在我们的套接字协议中
because clearly sending data back and
因为清楚地向回发送数据，
forth this is what we're here for
第四，这就是我们在这里
but as I said before when that Netflix
但是就像我之前所说的那样
team sat down and said we want to do
团队坐下来说我们想做
this better they didn't stop with I want
更好的是他们并没有停止我想要的
to transfer data better what they
更好地传输数据
actually sat down to do is they said I
其实坐下来是他们说我
want to make distributed communication
想要进行分布式通信
better right they didn't just stop by
更好的权利，他们不只是停下来
saying hey I just need request/response
说嘿，我只需要请求/响应
for these four things and some frames to
对于这四件事和一些框架
go back and forth what can we do in a
来回去我们可以做什么
protocol that allows us to remove a
协议，使我们可以删除
bunch of the overhead that we see with
我们看到的一堆开销
other distributed systems so one of the
其他分布式系统，因此
first things they did was that every
他们做的第一件事是
single frame that gets transferred back
单帧传回
and forth every single frame most frames
每个单帧来回大多数帧
has an optional metadata payload
具有可选的元数据有效载荷
associated with it and so we you you do
与它相关联，所以我们您
have to sort of define upfront hey I'm
必须先定义一下，嘿，我是
gonna send metadata and the metadata is
将发送元数据，而元数据是
going to be of this mind type so it's
将是这种思维类型，所以
totally unstructured you get to pick do
完全非结构化的选择
you want to send a bunch of JSON how
你想发送一堆JSON如何
long do you want to just send a string
你想只发送一个字符串吗
along do you want to send CSV along like
你想一起发送CSV吗？
as the metadata gives you enough
因为元数据给你足够
information so that you can decode what
信息，以便您可以解码
the metadata says and be on with your
元数据说，并与您
life right so it's super flexible and
生活是正确的，所以它超级灵活，
generally is used to carry metadata
通常用于携带元数据
about what's in the data payload so this
关于数据有效载荷中的内容
means now that across a single
现在意味着
connection you can actually send
您实际上可以发送的连接
heterogeneous types of data imagine a
异类数据想象
company that needs to send a bunch of
需要发送一堆的公司
social media to your phone some of it
社交媒体到您的手机中
might be texts some of them might be
可能是文本，其中一些可能是
images some of it might be video all
图片其中一些可能全部是视频
over the same connection because every
在同一连接上，因为每个
single payload that comes across they
他们遇到的单个有效载荷
have the ability to take a look at the
有能力看看
metadata associated with this frame and
与此框架关联的元数据和
say hey
说嘿
should I do code this as 141 we also
我应该将其编码为141吗？
have this idea of fragmentation payload
有碎片有效载荷的想法
grams so that must have said frames this
克，所以一定要说这个
was very late last night
昨晚很晚
payload frames have no maximum size this
有效负载帧没有最大大小
can't this was protocol that came from a
这不能是来自
company that's responsible which for
负责哪个公司
what is it the vast majority over 50% I
超过50％的人占绝大多数
think of all traffic on the internet
考虑互联网上的所有流量
they really like send you really big
他们真的很喜欢给你很大
high quality videos right so it's really
高品质的视频，所以它真的
great for serving those kinds of
非常适合服务于此类
payloads but the reality of the
有效载荷，但现实
situation is if I had to send you a
情况是我是否必须寄给您
frame to have your entire 4 gig you know
框架让您知道整个4个演出
high def HD 4k HDR video of the latest
最新高清高清4k HDR视频
Avengers movie or something in it you're
复仇者联盟电影或其中的某些内容
gonna die right your network connection
会杀死您的网络连接
can't handle that something like that
无法处理那样的事情
both tcp mt use and just general
tcp mt和通用
reliability so it has this idea of
可靠性，所以它有这样的想法
fragmentation but it's handled
碎片化但已处理
transparently you can say hey I know
透明地你可以说嘿我知道
that you know I probably even though I
即使我我也知道
need to send you 4 gigs I probably only
需要给您发送4场演出，我可能只
want to send it to you 1 Meg at a time
想要一次发送给您1 Meg
if 1 Meg fails we can go retry it have
如果1 Meg失败，我们可以重试
another crack at it I don't want to wait
我不想等待的另一个裂缝
for us to get to like 3.99 gigs and then
让我们喜欢3.99演出，然后
have to start that whole thing over
必须重新开始整个事情
again
再次
but the key thing is it's it's placed
但关键是它已经放置
into the stream and in such a way that
进入流中，以这种方式
it's completely transparent software
这是完全透明的软件
developers people sitting up and saying
开发人员坐起来说
request response go get me Avengers
请求响应去给我复仇者
movie stream back Avengers movie never
电影流回复仇者联盟电影从未
realized that this fragmentation happens
意识到这种分裂发生了
under the hood it allows you to continue
在引擎盖下，它可以让您继续
reasoning logically about requests and
关于请求的逻辑推理
semantics about how you know a I asked
关于你如何知道我问的语义
for a single payload and I get a single
一个有效载荷，我得到一个
payload but the protocol does allow you
有效负载，但协议确实允许您
to optimize for network conditions you
针对网络条件进行优化
are currently in there's also the idea
目前也有想法
of cancellation and this is something
取消，这是东西
that and almost no other protocols have
几乎没有其他协议
in turns out to be as we said a little
原来是我们所说的
bit earlier really really interesting
早一点真的很有趣
because cancellation is a single signal
因为取消只是一个信号
by the requester to say hey I asked you
由请求者说嘿我问过你
for some stuff and that might have been
对于一些东西，那可能是
really expensive for you to build so
建造起来真的很贵
just go ahead and stop doing that right
只是去做，停止做正确的事
request stream and channels obviously
明显请求流和频道
but even in something like request
但即使在类似请求中
response where I'm going to do a request
回应我要提出的要求
and maybe you're gonna you know you have
也许你会知道你有
to go do something expensive and come
去做一些昂贵的事
back with a single result like I don't
回到一个单一的结果，就像我不
know go calculate my
知道去计算我的
current credit rating or something like
当前的信用等级或类似的东西
that where I'm gonna get a single
我要去的地方
response but maybe I have switched off
响应，但也许我已关闭
and I've gone on to a completely
我已经完全
different bit of my banking application
我的银行业务申请的不同之处
so why don't you just go stop that
那你为什么不停下来
server side you can reclaim all the CPU
服务器端可以回收所有CPU
usage you were about to do and give it
您将要使用的用法并给它
to some other customer there's the idea
对其他客户来说，
of leasing as well so leasing is is a
也是租赁的一部分，所以租赁是
way for servers to communicate load back
服务器进行通信的方式
to clients so we said that with request
给客户，所以我们说有要求
and semantics a requester can say okay
以及请求者可以说的语义
we've got a connection
我们有联系
send me eight send me ten and I'm not
给我八个人给我十个人
going to send you another request for
将向您发送另一个请求
one of those until I'm ready to go but
直到我准备出发的其中之一
what's to stop me as the requester from
是什么阻止我成为请求者
absolutely spamming the server at the
绝对向服务器发送垃圾邮件
other end saying okay I need request
另一端说可以，我需要请求
requests MacArthur quick request all the
要求MacArthur快速要求所有
way like that right you could totally
这样的权利，你完全可以
take down a server and so the protocol
拆除服务器，因此协议
has built into it the way that the
内置了这样的方式
server can basically tell any client
服务器基本上可以告诉任何客户端
that's currently connected to it it can
当前连接到它可以
say hey you're allowed to send me ten
说嘿，你可以寄给我十张
requests over the next minute or you're
在一分钟后提出要求，否则您将
allowed to send me ten requests over the
允许向我发送十个请求
next hour and it's totally dynamic so
下一个小时，它是完全动态的，所以
you can imagine a scenario where the
您可以想象一个场景
server side is sending these leasing
服务器端正在发送这些租赁
notifications based on the current load
基于当前负载的通知
if you were the only person around
如果你是周围唯一的人
because you know it's the middle of the
因为你知道那是
night it's a European Bank and one or
晚上是一家欧洲银行，或者
two people are there maybe they get
两个人在那里也许他们得到了
unlimited right you get to do Inc dot
无限的权利，你去做公司点
max level requests over int dot there
那里的int点的最大级别请求
long dot max time right but then as
长点最大时间正确，但随后
people come up in the morning new
人们早上新来
leasing messages are sent out to say
租赁信息发出说
okay well now my CPU is up at 50 percent
好吧，现在我的CPU速度提高了50％
so now you don't get to ask me that many
所以现在你不必问我那么多
times and this really triggers
时代，这真的触发了
client-side load balancing really well
客户端负载平衡真的很好
because you can imagine an algorithm
因为你可以想象一个算法
there where I know I can connect to a
在那里我知道我可以连接到
bunch of different servers in my data
一堆不同的服务器在我的数据中
center and one of them is telling me
中心，其中一个告诉我
it's totally full no more load no don't
它完全满了，没有更多的负荷，没有
want to hear from you at all and so that
想要听到您的声音，以便
causes me to flip over to the next
使我跳到下一个
client and that's got Lisa still so I
客户，那仍然是丽莎，所以我
can go out and make it call to that
可以出去叫它
particular one instead open that
而是打开一个特定的
connection make those requests
连接发出这些请求
okay and finally pretty sure this is the
好，最后很确定这是
finally resume ability resume ability is
最终恢复能力恢复能力是
really really interesting and comes
真的很有趣，来了
about absolutely out of sort of the the
关于绝对的
the social media cases imagine a
社交媒体案例设想
scenario I have a phone I've got a
方案我有一个电话，我有一个
newsfeed going on my phone and I'm on
我的手机上正在播放新闻提要
Wi-Fi because I'm in here and I walk
Wi-Fi，因为我在这里散步
outside immediately my Wi-Fi drops and I
外面我的Wi-Fi掉线了，我
go onto the the the cellular network
进入蜂窝网络
right so now it's done that from the
好的，现在从
perspective of the server at the other
在另一个服务器的角度
side I my connection has died which
一边我我的连接已经死了
means I need to go back I need to
表示我需要回去
subscribe for all new changes and
订阅所有新更改，并
enumerate everything that's happened in
列举发生的一切
the last hour or something like that so
最后一小时之类的
I can refresh and refill my feed and you
我可以刷新并重新填充我的提要，你
can imagine trying to do that at global
可以想象在全球范围内尝试这样做
scale at a social network is really
在社交网络上的规模确实是
really difficult but now imagine it in
真的很困难，但现在想像一下
your use cases as well like clearly this
您的用例以及清楚的例子
is the really obvious horrible thing but
是真正显而易见的可怕的事情，但是
you can think of the same kind of thing
你可以想到同样的事情
where if you have people with
如果有人在哪里
intermittent connections having to
间歇性连接必须
reengage
重新介入
in efficiencies both in the network
网络的效率都很高
right we have to send all of that you
对，我们必须将所有这些都发送给您
know everything that happen in the last
知道最后发生的一切
two hours again and in the data center
再在数据中心两个小时
compute right this is where we end up
计算正确，这就是我们最终的目标
with a situation where we're just
在这种情况下
running servers creating a bunch of data
运行服务器创建大量数据
that the client probably already has so
客户可能已经有
built into the protocol totally
完全内置在协议中
transparent to the user is this idea
对用户透明的是这个想法
that both parties when they come back up
双方回来时
instead of saying okay I'm creating a
而不是说我创建一个
new connection you can instead say hey
新的连接，您可以说嘿
I'm creating or I want to resume the
我正在创建，或者我想恢复
connection I just had okay great so you
连接我就好了，所以你
want to resume tell me the last thing
想继续告诉我最后一件事
you saw I'll tell you the last thing I
你看到我会告诉你我的最后一件事
saw will synchronize what those two are
看到将同步这两个是
and then any piece of data that would
然后是任何会
have come in during that time they got
在那段时间进来
dropped by one party or the other just
被一方或另一方丢弃
gets resent right there's we don't sort
变得不满，我们没有排序
of describe exactly how you store the
准确描述您如何存储
data and how you identify what has been
数据以及您如何识别已发生的事情
sent and what hasn't been sent that's
已发送，尚未发送的是
implemented on a application by
由应用程序实施
application basis but maybe you have
应用基础，但也许你有
sort of a warm cache where you keep
保留的温暖缓存
really close track of things that might
真正密切关注可能发生的事情
get you know come and go over the second
让你知道来来去去第二
or over ten seconds and then maybe
或超过十秒钟，然后
there's a colder one where we might keep
有一个比较冷的地方
sort of less granularity over things
事情的细化程度较低
that might have been here a minute ago
一分钟前可能在这里
or five minutes ago things like that
或五分钟前的事情
but this basically gives you the ability
但这基本上给了你能力
to pick up where you left off and
去接你离开的地方
identify all of the frames you missed in
识别您错过的所有帧
that small amount of time since you were
自从你
last there this is really really key to
最后，这真的是关键
a lot of the use cases we see our socket
很多用例我们看到我们的套接字
using okay
使用还好
right on time great so our socket as I
准时准时很棒，所以我们和我一样
said is a bi-directional multiplexed
说是双向复用
message based binary protocol utilizes
基于消息的二进制协议利用
back pressure for its efficiency and
效率高的背压
predictability provides primitives for
可预测性为
the four common interaction models
四种常见的互动模型
flexibility almost anywhere transport
几乎可以在任何地方运输的灵活性
language programming model let us know
语言编程模型让我们知道
what you want to use and all of those
您想使用什么以及所有这些
other features we sort of ran through at
我们在运行的其他功能
the end so with that let me first thank
最后，让我首先感谢
you all for coming here and sitting in
大家都来这里坐下
this giant room and I'm happy to answer
这个巨大的房间，我很乐意回答
questions up here thank you
问题在这里谢谢
[Applause]
[掌声]
[Music]
[音乐]